OKAY, SHE IS THE STAR
OF THE PLAY
AND SHE IS
MY GIRLFRIEND.
I GET TO HAVE SEX
WITH THE STAR
OF THE PLAY.
PEOPLE CAN HEAR YOU.
I KNOW!
WOW, SHE LOOKS GREAT,
DOESN'T SHE?
( grunts )
Man:
HI.
THAT IS ONE
GOOD-LOOKING MAN.
IS IT JUST ME
OR CAN YOU ACTUALLY
SEE HIS ABS
THROUGH HIS OVERCOAT?
Man:
SO, YOU BEEN DOING THIS LONG?
Kathy:
NO, YOU'RE MY FIRST.
PUT THE MONEY ON THE TABLE.
( passionate moaning )
Man:
OH, YEAH, OH, YEAH,
THAT'S NICE.
( moaning continues )
DUDE.
Man:
IS THAT AN EXPENSIVE BLOUSE?
Kathy:
IF YOU WANT IT TO BE.
( fabric ripping )
Kathy:
OH!
HERE'S YOUR
GIRLFRIEND'S BUTTON.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
OH, HEY, MON,
DO YOU STILL HAVE
YOUR OLD BLOUSES AND DRESSES
FROM HIGH SCHOOL?
YEAH, I THINK I HAVE SOME
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE. WHY?
IT'S JUST MATERNITY CLOTHES
ARE SO EXPENSIVE.
Monica:
RACH, I MADE
A PILE OF YOUR STUFF
ON THIS SIDE
OF THE ROOM.
IF YOU COULD JUST...
( grunts )
THROW YOUR PURSES AT IT?
BLOOMINGDALE'S ELIMINATED
MY DEPARTMENT.
( gasps )
GOD! ARE YOU OUT
OF A JOB?
NO, BUT THEY STUCK ME
IN PERSONAL SHOPPING
WHICH IS JUST
A HUGE STEP DOWN.
"PERSONAL SHOPPING"--
WHAT IS THAT?
LIKE, WHERE WALK AROUND
WITH SNOOTY RICH PEOPLE
AND TELL THEM WHAT TO BUY?
UH-HUH.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
HEY.
UM... EXCUSE ME.
WE SWITCHED APARTMENTS.
YOU CAN'T EAT OUR FOOD ANYMORE.
THAT GRAVY TRAIN HAS ENDED.
THERE'S GRAVY?
IF YOU HAVE THE BIG APARTMENT
YOU HAVE TO DEAL WITH PEOPLE
COMING OVER ALL THE TIME.
THAT FRIDGE HAS GOT
TO BE STOCKED, OKAY?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THINK I LEFT
A DONUT UP HERE.
HEY.
OH, HOW WAS
KATHY'S PLAY?
WELL, KATHY GETS HALF-NAKED
AND SIMULATES SEX
WITH A REAL
GOOD-LOOKING GUY.
IT WAS LIKE SOMEBODY LITERALLY
WROTE DOWN MY WORST NIGHTMARE
AND THEN CHARGED ME
$32 TO SEE IT.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA
FOR A BUSINESS.
I'M TOTALLY SCREWED, OKAY?
THEY'RE GOING TO BE
HOT AND HEAVY
ON STAGE EVERY NIGHT
AND THEY'RE GOING TO GO
TO THEIR CAST PARTIES
AND HE'LL TRY TO UNDERMINE ME.
"SO, WHERE'S YOUR BOYFRIEND--
WHAT HIS NAME, CHESTER?"
AND SHE'LL GO,
"NO, IT'S CHANDLER."
AND HE'LL GO, "WHATEVER."
( pained laughter )
THAT-THAT IS
A GOOD TRICK.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, LOOK,
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
LOOK, THEY'RE THERE
TO DO A JOB.
JUST 'CAUSE THEY
WORK TOGETHER
DOESN'T MEAN
THEY'LL GET TOGETHER.
JUST BECAUSE IT HAPPENED
WITH SUSAN SARANDON
AND TIM ROBBINS
DOESN'T MEAN IT'LL
HAPPEN WITH THEM.
OH, OH...
ALEC BALDWIN
AND KIM BASINGER.
OH! TOM CRUISE
AND NICOLE KIDMAN.
YEAH.
MEL GIBSON AND CLINT EASTWOOD.
THEY'RE NOT A COUPLE.
OH, OKAY! I GET THE GAME NOW.
LOOK, LET ME
ASK YOU A QUESTION:
WHEN THEY WERE
DOING IT ON STAGE
WAS IT, LIKE,
REALLY HOT?
OH, YEAH.
WELL, OKAY
SO THEN YOU'RE FINE.
LOOK, THE RULE IS
WHEN TWO ACTORS ARE
ACTUALLY DOING IT OFF STAGE
THEN ALL THE SEXUAL TENSION
BETWEEN THEM IS GONE, OKAY?
SO AS LONG AS
IT'S HOT ON STAGE
YOU GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
IT'S WHEN THE HEAT
GOES AWAY--
THAT'S WHEN
YOU'RE IN TROUBLE.
REALLY?
YOU HAVE BEEN TO EVERY
PLAY I'VE BEEN IN.
HAVE I EVER HAD CHEMISTRY?
All:
NO.
NO!
SO, MAN, ARE YOU GOING
TO GO SEE THE PLAY
WITH ME TONIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW
HOW COMFORTABLE I AM
GOING TO SEE
HOW HOT THE SEX IS
BETWEEN SOME GUY
AND YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT...
NO, NO. OH, I'M THERE.
HEY.
Joey:
HEY, MON.
WANT PANCAKES?
YOU MADE PANCAKES?
YEAH. GRAB A PLATE.
NO, NO. STAY RIGHT THERE.
GETTING CLOSER.
OKAY, OKAY,
BUT DON'T WORRY
BECAUSE WE ALSO HAVE
CEREALS, MUFFINS, WAFFLES
AND JAMS, JELLIES
AND MARMALADES--
WHICH I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN
ARE THE SAME THING.
LISTEN, ALSO,
WE'RE WATCHING
THE GAME HERE SATURDAY NIGHT
IF PEOPLE WANT TO COME OVER.
OH, YEAH.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
HAVING PEOPLE OVER.
OH, YEAH?
WHO'S PLAYING?
THE PLAYERS.
SOMEBODY SEEMS
TO BE MISSING
BEING THE HOSTESS.
( chuckles ):
PLEASE.
IT'S A RELIEF,
IS WHAT IT IS
IS WHAT IT IS.
PHEEBS, STICK OUT
YOUR PLATE.
MONICA, I'M QUITTING.
I JUST HELPED AN 81-YEAR-OLD
WOMAN PUT ON A THONG
AND SHE DIDN'T EVEN BUY IT.
I'M TELLING YOU, I'M QUITTING.
THAT'S IT.
I'M TALKING TO MY BOSS
RIGHT NOW.
YES, I AM.
YES, I AM. YES, I AM.
CALL ME
WHEN YOU GET THIS MESSAGE.
OH, MR. WALTHAM.
I, UH... REALLY NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
IN A MOMENT, PLEASE.
I'M IN THE MIDDLE
OF A TASK
AND YOU HAVE A CUSTOMER.
HI.
HI. I'M JOSHUA.
HI. I'M RACHEL GREEN.
WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU, JOSHUA?
WELL, I NEED
A WHOLE NEW WARDROBE.
MY WIFE...
WELL, MY EX-WIFE...
OH, I'M SO SORRY.
ANYWAY, SHE BURNED
ALL OF MY CLOTHES.
I GOT AWAY WITH TWO THINGS--
THIS SUIT
AND WHAT TURNED OUT
TO BE A SKIRT.
WELL, AT LEAST
THAT'S A GREAT SUIT.
BUT IT WASN'T MUCH FUN
DROPPING IT OFF
AT THE DRY CLEANERS
IN THE SKIRT.
I NEED EVERYTHING
DOWN TO UNDERWEAR
SO IF YOU'RE WILLING
I'M, UH... I'M ALL YOURS.
OKAY.
RACHEL, YOU NEEDED
TO SPEAK TO ME?
NO, NO,
THAT WASN'T ME.
WELL...
WE SHOULD GET STARTED.
LET ME SHOW YOU MY UNDERWEAR--
THE SELECTION OF UNDERWEAR
THAT WE CARRY.
OH, IT'S THIS WAY.
IT'S THIS WAY.
IT'S THIS WAY?
YEAH.
SORRY.
( sighs )
I'M RIGHT, RIGHT?
THERE WAS, LIKE,
NO CHEMISTRY BETWEEN THEM.
BEFORE THEY HAD HEAT.
NOW THERE'S NO HEAT.
NOW, YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MEANS.
JOEY TOLD US WHAT THIS MEANS.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S NOT JUMP
TO ANY CONCLUSIONS.
THERE WAS SOME SEXUAL
CHEMISTRY BETWEEN THEM.
COME ON, IT WAS LIKE COUSINS
HAVING SEX.
HERE SHE COMES.
DON'T SAY A WORD.
JUST BE COOL.
DON'T BE, YOU KNOW, YOU.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HEY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING AGAIN.
DID YOU LIKE IT?
ABSOLUTELY.
MM-HMM.
WASN'T NICK FUNNY
WHEN HE COULDN'T GET
HIS MATCH LIT?
( chuckling stiffly )
IT'S A GOOD PLAY,
ISN'T IT?
MM.
I LOVED THE PLAY.
UH... YEAH,
YOU WERE GREAT
AND NICK-- DITTO.
CLEARLY, YOU'RE
HAVING SEX WITH HIM.
OKAY...
CLEARLY, I'M HAVING
SEX WITH HIM?
IT WAS SO OBVIOUS!
THERE WAS NO CHEMISTRY
BETWEEN YOU.
OKAY, LET ME
JUST GET THIS STRAIGHT:
YOU'RE ACCUSING ME
OF CHEATING ON YOU
AND YOU'RE INSULTING
MY PERFORMANCE?
I CAN SEE HOW
THIS COULD HAPPEN.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
UP THERE EVERY NIGHT
NAKED, TOUCHING,
KISSING.
ACTING.
CHANDLER,
THIS IS MY JOB.
I-I'M PLAYING
A PART IN A PLAY.
HOW CAN YOU
NOT TRUST ME?
WELL, YOU CAN UNDERSTAND,
GIVEN HOW WE STARTED.
OH, WOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE
THROWING THAT IN MY FACE.
THAT IS WHAT HAPPENED
AND I DON'T EVEN SEE YOU
DENYING THIS.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
CHANDLER.
WHY DON'T YOU CALL ME
WHEN YOU GROW UP?
YEAH, WELL
DON'T EXPECT THAT
TO HAPPEN ANYTIME SOON.
OH! I HAVE THE BEST JOB
IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
THE MOST ADORABLE GUY
CAME OVER TODAY
AND I GOT
TO DRESS HIM UP ALL DAY.
RACHEL HAS A NEW DOLL.
OH, I WISH HE WAS A DOLL.
THEN I COULD GET A "RACHEL" DOLL
AND I'D BUMP THEM TOGETHER
AND MAKE KISSING NOISES.
OH, AND HE'S GOT THE
MOST BEAUTIFUL NAME.
I NEVER REALIZED.
JOSHUA. JOSH... U-A.
JOSHUA. JOSH...
UH... HELLO.
HI...
OH, WHAT DO I SMELL?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IT SMELLS GOOD.
FRESH COOKIES,
HOT FROM THE OVEN.
PLEASE, HAVE SOME.
OH, YO...
I'VE JUST BEEN FIDDLING AROUND
IN HERE
MAKING DELICIOUS TREATS
FOR EVERYONE.
OH. THE NEW PLAYBOY.
YEAH. JUST SOMETHING
I PICKED UP.
COOKIES AND PORN.
YOU'RE THE BEST MOM EVER!
( giggles )
WHAT? WHAT?
NOTHING. JUST SOMETHING
JOSHUA SAID ABOUT V NECKS
BUT YOU HAD TO BE THERE.
YEAH, HOW DOES, UH,
JASON LOOK IN A V NECK?
IT'S JOSHUA.
OH, WHATEVER.
WAIT... WAIT.
THIS... THIS ISN'T TAKEOUT.
WELL, HATE TO EAT AND RUN.
NO, WAIT.
PLEASE DON'T GO.
I'VE GOT PORN FOR YOU, TOO.
ME, I DON'T NEED IT.
PEOPLE ARE SUPPOSED TO WANT
TO HANG OUT HERE.
WHY?
HONEY, WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL?
I'M THE HOSTESS.
NOT THOSE GUYS.
I'M ALWAYS THE HOSTESS.
I MEAN, EVEN WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
I MEAN THE...
THE GIRLS BROUGHT THEIR DOLLIES
TO MY TEA PARTY.
I SERVED THE BEST AIR.
WELL, WHY DID YOU MAKE,
LIKE, A WHOLE BIG THING
OUT OF, YOU KNOW, EVERYONE
HAS TO HANG OUT
IN THE BIG APARTMENT?
BECAUSE THEY TOOK OUR APARTMENT.
I WANTED TO PUNISH THEM.
I'M-I'M DONE NOW.
THEY-THEY-THEY'VE
SUFFERED ENOUGH.
BUT IF YOU WANTED TO PUNISH THEM
YOU SHOULD HAVE JUST MADE THEM
HANG OUT HERE.
ALL RIGHT THEN,
WHEN I'M FINISHED
WITH THIS PLACE
IT'S GOING TO BE
TEN TIMES BETTER
THAN THAT PLACE.
OH, ARE WE GOING
TO TRASH THEIR PLACE?
STEPS!
SLUT!
( slurring ):
YOU WILL ALL BE
VERY HAPPY TO HEAR
THAT KATHY IS SLEEPING
WITH THAT GUY.
WHAT?
OH, NO.
OH, GOD.
SO, YOU
WERE RIGHT?
I CONFRONTED HER
AND SHE DIDN'T DENY IT.
I DON'T LIVE HERE.
CHANDLER...
Monica:
CHANDLER, WHAT
DID SHE SAY?
WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU SURE?
WELL, I MAY BE DRUNK
BUT I KNOW WHAT SHE SAID
SO THEN I WENT OVER
TO BEEFSTEAK CHULIE'S...
YES! SEE, YOU AND I
HAVE ALWAYS BEEN LIKE...
WHOOPS.
OH, HEY, DO YOU
NEED HELP WITH THAT?
NO. I GOT IT.
OH, I JUST FEEL BAD.
I NEVER VACUUM.
HI.
HEY.
SO, I WAS WITH JOSHUA
FOR AN HOUR TODAY
AND HE HAS NOT ASKED ME OUT.
JUST SO FRUSTRATING.
WHY DON'T YOU
ASK HIM OUT?
OH, YEAH. TOTALLY.
THAT'S SUCH A TURN-ON.
REALLY?
IT DOESN'T SEEM DESPERATE?
THAT'S THE TURN-ON.
HE JUST GOT A
DIVORCE, RIGHT?
SO, HE'S PROBABLY
REALLY NERVOUS
AROUND WOMEN,
YOU KNOW?
MAYBE YOU JUST NEED
TO MAKE THE FIRST MOVE.
I'VE NEVER ASKED
A GUY OUT BEFORE.
YOU'VE NEVER ASKED A GUY OUT?
NO. HAVE YOU?
THOUSANDS OF TIMES.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ME
SOUND TOO GOOD, DOES IT?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW I WOULD GO ABOUT IT.
OH, WELL, WHAT I DO IS, UH...
I LOOK A WOMAN UP AND DOWN
AND I SAY,
"HEY... HOW YOU DOIN'?"
OH, PLEASE.
HEY... HOW YOU DOIN'?
OKAY.
I'M GOING TO DO THAT.
I'M GOING TO CALL HIM UP
AND I'M GOING TO ASK HIM OUT.
I CAN DO THAT... ASK HIM OUT.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
HI, JOSHUA... IT'S RACHEL GREEN
FROM BLOOMINGDALE'S.
YEAH, UM...
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF YOU,
UM... IF YOU, UM...
LEFT YOUR WALLET
AT THE STORE TODAY?
OH, WELL
WE FOUND A WALLET AND WE...
THE LICENSE... WELL,
THAT IS A GOOD IDEA.
UH, WELL, LET'S SEE.
THIS LICENSE
BELONGS TO A, UH...
BELONGS TO A MR....
UH, PHEEBS...
AND, UM... YEAH.
SO, OKAY... SO SORRY
TO BOTHER YOU AT HOME.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
BYE.
YOU'VE DONE THAT
A THOUSAND TIMES?
I'VE NEVER DONE THAT.
OH, GOD. I JUST GOT SO NERVOUS
THAT HE WAS GOING TO SAY NO.
WELL, YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE HIM
SOMETHING HE CAN'T SAY NO TO
LIKE, UH, KNICKS TICKETS.
INVITE THE GUY TO A KNICKS GAME.
YOU'RE GUARANTEED HE'LL SAY YES.
AND THAT WILL WORK?
ABSOLUTELY...
IF IT DOESN'T, CAN I
GET THE EXTRA TICKET?
( loud whirring )
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?
DID SHE CALL?
NO. SORRY.
WELL, MAY...
MAYBE I SHOULD CALL HER.
Joey:
FORGET HER, MAN.
YOU DON'T NEED HER.
YOU DON'T NEED THAT.
HE'S RIGHT. WHAT SHE DID
WAS UNFORGIVABLE.
WELL, YEAH, BUT... YOU KNOW,
WHAT-WHAT IF I WAS WRONG?
HOW MIGHT YOU BE WRONG?
WELL, YOU KNOW, WHAT IF SHE
DIDN'T ACTUALLY SLEEP
WITH THE GUY?
TELL ME SHE ACTUALLY
TOLD YOU.
SHE DID NOT HAVE TO TELL ME.
I SAW THE PLAY
AND THERE WAS NO HEAT.
BACK ME UP, ROSS.
THAT'S ALL YOU'RE
BASING THIS ON?
THAT'S NOT BACKING ME UP!
YOU SAID WITH THE OFFSTAGE
AND THE HEAT
AND THE ONSTAGE AND HEAT...
WHOA-WHOA! THAT WAS
JUST A THEORY.
THERE'S A LOT OF THEORIES
THAT DIDN'T PAN OUT...
LONE GUNMAN...
COMMUNISM... GEOMETRY.
OH, MY GOD!
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO
TO A BASKETBALL GAME WITH...
YOU KNOW,
IT'S FUNNY... BASKETBALL
BECAUSE I HAPPEN
TO HAVE TICKETS TO THE...
OKAY... UM...
WHO LIKES THE KNICK...?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH... WELL,
AS A SINGLE WOMAN...
WHO IS AVAILABLE
I THINK YOU
LOOK GREAT.
HUH... YEAH?
YEP. OH, YEAH.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
OH, YEAH. YEAH,
THIS LOOKS GREAT.
UM, SO, YOU LIKE IT?
I DO. I DO. I LOVE IT.
IN FACT, I-I THINK
I'M GOING TO WEAR IT HOME.
GREAT.
ALL RIGHT. WELL,
THANK YOU SO MUCH...
OH... SURE.
FOR ALL
YOUR HELP.
WELL, I GUESS, UH,
I GUESS THIS IS IT.
YEEAAH!
THANKS.
MAYBE I'LL SEE YOU
IN THE SPRING
UH, FOR THE
BATHING SUITS.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO DO THAT NOW?!
OH, THAT'S OKAY... I...
OH...
ANYWAY, HOPEFULLY I-I'LL
SEE YOU AROUND SOMETIME.
BASKETBALL!
SORRY?
I, UH... I HAVE TWO TICKETS
TO THE KNICKS GAME TONIGHT
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED...
JUST AS A THANK YOU
FOR THIS WEEK.
WOW! THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
REALLY?
YEAH, THAT WOULD
BE FANTASTIC.
OH...
MY NEPHEW IS CRAZY
ABOUT THE KNICKS.
THIS IS FANTASTIC.
THANK YOU
SO MUCH, RACHEL.
GOOD MORNING.
HI.
HEY.
HEY... I JUST... I JUST
WANTED TO COME OVER
TO... TO SAY
THAT I'M SORRY, YOU KNOW.
I KNOW... I ACTED LIKE
THE BIGGEST IDIOT IN THE WORLD
AND I CAN COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU WERE SO UPSET.
OH, WOW.
I REALLY WISH
YOU'D CALLED ME.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I WISH I HAD, TOO
BUT, YOU KNOW, I-I THINK
THIS IS A GOOD THING, YOU KNOW
'CAUSE WE'VE HAD
OUR FIRST FIGHT
AND NOW WE CAN MOVE ON.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN
I KNOW FOR ME...
NICK'S PANTS?
YEAH.
WELL...
I THINK OUR SECOND FIGHT
IS GOING TO BE A BIG ONE.
Joey:
OKAY...
FOR NEXT TIME,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I HAVE AN EXTRA TICKET...
AN EXTRA TICKET...
NOT TWO TICKETS.
I HAVE AN EXTRA TICKET.
RIGHT.
SO, THE FIRST TIME
YOU ASKED A GUY OUT
HE-HE TURNED YOU DOWN?
HE DIDN'T TURN ME DOWN.
HE'S AT THE GAME, ISN'T HE?
I GOT THE DATE.
I'M JUST NOT ON IT.
OKAY... IT'S READY.
COME ON.
WHAT'S READY?
JUST COME.
OH, MY GOD...
WOW!
HEY...
MONICA...
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
OH, DID YOU-WHAT,
DID YOU WORK FOR
TWO DAYS STRAIGHT?
PRETTY MUCH.
SO, WHAT-WHAT DO YOU
THINK OF THE FLOOR?
I DON'T KNOW.
LOOKS THE SAME.
YOU USED TO HAVE CARPET.
OH, YEAH.
SO, I-I MADE SNACKS.
OH.
PLEASE, JUST HANG OUT, OKAY.
I-I'M JUST GOING TO REST MY EYES
FOR JUST A LITTLE BIT.
MON, DO YOU WANT US
TO, UH, COME BACK LATER?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
STAY, STAY, STAY.
JUST KEEP TALKING.
I AM ALWAYS THE HOSTESS.
HEY.
HOW DID IT GO?
WELL, SHE WASN'T
SLEEPING WITH HIM.
OH, GOOD.
SHE IS NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I'M SAYING THAT
SHE IS A DEVIL WOMAN.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN,
YOU THINK YOU KNOW A PERSON.
THEN THEY TURN AROUND,
THEY SLEEP WITH NICK.
NICK AND HIS ROCK-HARD PECS
AND HIS GIANT MAN NIPPLES.
I HATE HIM...
AND I HATE HER.
WELL, I DON'T HATE HER.
I LOVE HER.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT, REALLY.
HOW? HOW IS IT
YOUR FAULT?
BECAUSE... AAH! I...
I SHOULD HAVE CALLED.
YOU KNOW, IF I HAD JUST
CALLED HER
AFTER OUR BIG, STUPID FIGHT
SHE NEVER WOULD HAVE
GONE OUT WITH NICK
AND THEY WOULDN'T HAVE
ENDED UP IN BED TOGETHER.
I THREW HER
AT HIS MAN NIPPLES.
HONEY, THIS IS
NOT YOUR FAULT.
JUST BECAUSE YOU
GUYS HAD A FIGHT
DOES NOT JUSTIFY HER
SLEEPING WITH SOMEONE.
WELL, IF-IF SHE THOUGHT
THEY WERE ON A BREAK...
ONE OF YOUR CUSTOMERS SEEMS
TO HAVE LEFT HIS BILLFOLD--
A JOSHUA BURGIN.
REALLY?
WILL YOU CALL HIM?
YES. I WILL, ABSOLUTELY.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
( in a deep voice ):
HELLO, RACHEL.
HI, JOSHUA.
I LEFT MY WALLET HERE
ON PURPOSE.
REALLY?
YES. I JUST WANTED
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
OH, I'M GLAD.
RACHEL, I'D LIKE
TO SAY SOMETHING TO YOU.
YES?
HOW YOU DOIN'?